thesparklingminds.com 2009-05-02

# The Sparkling Minds: Default Page

Thank you for visiting our educational games web site ("website") located at "thesparklingminds.com". Through this website, we aim to provide a safe, clean environment delivering educational content to children (PreSchool - Grade IV) in the form of scientifically designed computer games. We understand the importance of privacy concerns, especially in the Internet environment and are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of the personal information of all users of this website. Our policy on the collection and use of personal information and other information is outlined below. 

**Information submitted by Users**  
In certain portions of our website, we may collect "personally identifiable information" from users. "Personally identifiable information" includes, for example, a person's name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, or any other information that can be used to identify or contact an individual, whether online or offline. We may collect this primarily for the following purposes: 

  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of the website,
  * To deliver services such as Scorecard tracking, Educational programs, Information, Newsletters or any other services you request or purchase
  * To alert you on special offers, updated information and other new services from The Sparkling Minds or to forward promotional materials 
  * To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us or Order Inquiry
  * On all areas of our website, we seek to collect personally identifiable information only from adults. If you e-mail us, you are voluntarily releasing information to us. Your e-mail address will be used by us to respond to you. We will not use the information that can identify you for direct marketing purposes.

**Information Collected Automatically**  
We also collect information by various technical means, without the user submitting any information, in order to monitor the usage of our website (such as the number of visitors to our website and the most popular games) and to improve the user experience (such as saving your preferences). The information collected in this way generally is not personally identifiable information.

We also collect data automatically through "cookies" and "web logs" which are commonly used on the Internet. A "cookie" is a piece of information that a web site transfers to a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. As a user moves across pages on our website, a cookie is used to tell us that it is the same user. We also may use a cookie to keep track of your preferences. You may set your browser to accept or not accept cookies and you may delete any cookies that you have received. However, should you decide to delete/disable any cookies we place on your computer, some of our website features may not work as expected.

We also maintain web logs that record basic information about visitors to our website such as the IP address for their computers and the type of browser and operating system they use. An IP address is a number designated for your computer by your Internet service provider to provide access to the Internet. We may use your IP address to gather aggregate information on the use of the website, but we will only be able to identify you individually if we link the IP address to you as a particular user. 

**Additional Uses and Disclosures of Information**  
We may disclose and use the information we collect in connection with investigations of illegal or unauthorized activity or in response to requests by law enforcement agencies as well as government and other authorities. We may disclose information to protect our rights or property or other users of the website. In the event that 'The Sparkling Minds' is acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, information we collect on our website may be one of the transferred assets. We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our website and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user. 

**Security**  
We will protect the security and integrity of sensitive information collected on our website. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

In some areas of our website, you may establish access through a username and a password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your password. 

In the unlikely event that the security of your personally identifiable information in our control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development through your active e-mail address. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. 

**Third Parties**  
For your convenience, this page may contain certain hyperlinks to other sites outside our website. In addition, you may have linked to our website from another site. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites, even if you access those using links from our website. We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit, or link from, and contact the owners or operators of such sites if you have any concerns or questions. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
Whenever this Privacy Policy changes, we will update the changes immediately on our website. If you do not agree to the changes, please do not continue to use the website. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our website or sending you an e-mail if we have your e-mail address. If you are concerned about our use of your personal information, please log your comment using the contact form located at  http://www.thesparklingminds.com/Feedback.aspx (under the category "General Feedback").
